Hello Hello Friends Welcome to this channel,
here we help you in such situations in
which you are confused about which
product is better for you and which
product you should buy. Today we will talk about
such an insurance company and its
product which is leading in the market
and provides vest balance. So
before moving ahead in the video, you must
subscribe to this channel and like the video.
So friends, today we will talk about Religare
Health Insurance's Airline which is
currently running in the market. We
take an example for illustration in
which there will be a problem of 5 lakhs and four
members will be deducted. So let us understand its features. The
first feature is Blueprint. There will be no typing
on room rent on a policy of 5 lakhs or above,
as many companies do,
in this there are 162 calories of Sameshwar. Here
in Daily Wear's Airline, you will be
provided with a quintal Kajol Pingal private room, no matter how much it is. The only
condition is that your Sameshwar should be
minimum 5 black. The second option is
IEC print.  As in many companies, there is a
capping of two percent of sum assured
on the ICU rate, that is, if someone has
taken a five lakh policy, then he does
not get more than 1000 ICU coverage, but there is
no such capping in Religare's AirPlan, whatever be the ICU rate,
Religare's AirPlan will cover it. If
your policy is of Rs 5 lakh or more, then the
third feature is of automatic recharge, as
Religare's Care Plan is automatically
recharged up to hundred percent, for
example, suppose there are
four members in the policy and one member has
taken four lakhs in a policy of Rs 5 lakh, then at that time only Rs 1 lakh
is outstanding from the policy, if it is used then with the help of
Religare's automatic recharge, if
after the last one, any other member
needs the plan again, then
Religare's recharge option will automatically recharge the policy, there is
no extra premium for that, the
policy will
automatically get recharged and increase by another Rs 5 lakh, as per Anjana's understanding.  It will
mean that overall a customer can spend up to ₹10
and the feature is free hospitalization.
In April, Religare offers 30 days
free hospitalization.
Suppose someone is hospitalized
for 2 days, then the company will pay for that hospitalization.
Plus, in reimbursement,
whatever expenses
related to the disease have been incurred before 30 days, you can also claim that from the company.
Similarly, our fifth feature is
hospitalization which covers selected S, that is,
if it is covered in the policy, then
apart from fertilization,
whatever expenses will be incurred
on that disease after six days of observation, you can claim that from the company. The
feature is no claim bonus.
Religare's Airplane
gives you options for different types of no claim bonus. The first
option is 50% bonus, which you will get
automatically in the Main Clear Care policy and the
second option is End C also
Super in which the
company will give you a no claim bonus of 150%. For this, you will have to pay some
extra money to the company. For example
If we talk in terms of terms, suppose someone has
taken a policy of 10 lakhs and he has
taken the normal NCP option, then his policy will
increase by 10 percent every year and
after five years it will increase by 50% from 10 to 11, 12, 13,
14 and 15 to 1500000 and if
any customer has given such an option in
which he
gets a Bigg Boss of one fifty percent, then in that policy,
60 percent missile will be given in the first year, 60 percent in the
third year, 10 percent in the fourth year and
10 percent in the fifth year and that
policy will increase to 25 lakhs. The seventh
feature is organ donor. It is reported that if any
policy holder needs an organ transplant, then the
company will bill the hospital expenses of the organ donor only. The
eighth feature which is the USP of our Religare
Airline is free annual health
checkup, that is, you get free annual health checkup every year whether the policy is
clean or not.
All members of the policy will get a checkup. There
is no chatting for this and this is a cashless option.
You don't have to claim any reimbursement for this, you
just have to go to one of the company's centres
and get your test done. The
list of annual health checkup varies with
you on the condition. If you have completed the Chhath fast worth Rs. 3 lakh
or Rs. 4 lakh, then
you will
get free tests of fruit in the group, vase, eating sugar syrup, cholesterol, SGPT serum, kidney and ECG. If you have
taken a policy of Rs. 5 lakh or Rs. 10 lakh, then you will get
free routine blood group, fasting blood sugar, lipid profile, kidney function test and ECG from the company. And if you have
taken a plan bigger than that, then you will also get ABC
in routine blood group, casting sugar,
lipid profile, TMT test, all these tests. The
next feature is ambulance news.
This policy covers your ambulance up to Rs. 1580, 3000. The
next feature is End Opinion
Benefit.  In the Religare Care plan, you
get this feature that if a policy holder suffers from
such a disease for which he
wants to take the opinion of another doctor, then
Religare will provide him
free of cost treatment for second registration. The
next feature is AYUSH
treatment. Alternative treatments like
AYUSH will be covered in this policy and you
can also claim for a commission from the company.
If this feature is for day care procedures,
then Religare's Airplane 551 covers day care
procedures. The next feature is
domiciliary fertilization. If
in any condition the patient has to get treatment at home
and instead of
going to the doctor, he has to make hospital arrangements at home.
In such a condition, there is an
encounter mode of injury at the time of the policy, that is, if it is a Tasla
policy, then you can claim a claim of up to Rs 1 lakh from the
company in domiciliary hospitalization.
Religare Care Priyanka
Alva has a feature. When you
purchase the policy, you will get some extra money.
You can get the alarm added to your policy for example, suppose
you have
selected Husain Delhi Aloo, then
you will get telecom benefit on fertilization and wife insurance. For
example, if
someone is
admitted in the hospital for four days, then the policy will cover the
previous insurance and along with it, the
company will give you an extra cash benefit of Rs 20,000 for four days.
We also have some optional covers
like unlimited automatic recharge, that is, the
automatic recharge
feature of the policy, then you can avail unlimited time,
but the options are everyday care, third is OPD
care and for this tele alarms.
Religare's Airplan has some such features
which are not available in any other company's plan,
like Aligarh's care plan, robotic
surgery, stem cell therapy, major Michael Kind
class's oral chemotherapy, mental illness, it
also covers all these things. It was said that
Airplan also covers bariatric surgery,
also reduces intravenous injections
and such  There are many features that
you will get in the settled year. And if we talk about
OPD and waiting period, that is,
pre-existing diseases, if the policy
holder who is purchasing the policy
already has any disease, then he cannot claim for
that disease even after 4 years by informing the company about this disease. So, if
we
talk about waiting period in this, then there are some
diseases which will have a waiting period of 2 years.
I will also share with you the names of some diseases
which will be covered after 2 years,
such as piles, heartburn, cataract,
callus, ulcers, ulcers, ulcers, nails, polish, aspirins, varicose veins, etc.
In Religare's share policy,
accident is covered by decision and after 30 days,
all such diseases which do
not take much time to develop or which are
not in the list of meeting dates of 2 years, all
those are covered, that is, you will get coverage
for almost all the diseases after 10 days
and all the
diseases will be covered after 10 years. There are some permanent
exclusions of Religare.
As per the policy, if the dental treatment is not due to an accident, then the
dental treatment due to an accident will be covered in this policy. The
second question is if there is any disease which is caused by
cricket itself, like if there is
any disease caused by alcohol addiction, then that
policy will never be covered. I would
suggest you that everyone should buy Religare's Care Policy
and to buy this policy
you can also call me, my number will be
flashing on your screen.
Thank you very much for watching the video.